Guide to the Cass Gilbert Papers and Architectural Drawings 1883-1952 (Bulk 1900-1934) PR 21
New-York Historical Society
- Series X. Architectural Drawings, 1883-1952
  - PR21.333: Col. Z. S. Spalding, Office Building (Portland, Or.), 1908-1910
  - PR21.334: Springfield Municipal Building (Springfield, Mass.)
    - Longitudinal and transverse sections. graphite on paper. (Object PR21.334.O1)
    - Pynchon Street and side elevations. graphite on paper. (Object PR21.334.O2)
    - Site plan. ink on board. (Object PR21.334.O3)
  - PR21.335: G. C. Squires Residence (Saint Paul, Minn.)
    - Sketch [exterior perspective]. watercolor on board. (Object PR21.335.O1)
    - Front perspective study. ink on board. (Object PR21.335.O2)
    - "Sketch of house for Mr. G C Squires Summit Court" [perspective study]. watercolor on paper, hinged to board. (Object PR21.335.O3)
  - PR21.336: State Savings Bank (Butte, Mont.), 1906
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-87)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-88)
  - PR21.337: Alexander Stewart Apartment House
    - Exterior perspective study. graphite on trace and board (broken). (Object PR21.337.O1)
      Housed with PR21.3.O1
  - PR21.338: Stone House (Saint Paul, Minn.), 1890
  - PR21.339: Lane K. Stone Cottage (White Bear Lake, Minn.), 1892
  - PR21.340: Strickland House (Ellsworth, Wis.)
    - Study for a house [exterior perspective]. watercolor on trace and board. (Object PR21.340.O1)
    - First floor plan. ink on paper and board. (Object PR21.340.O2)
    - Second floor plan. ink on paper and board. (Object PR21.340.O3)
  - PR21.341: E. C. Stringer House (Saint Paul, Minn.)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-90)
  - PR21.342: Strong and Sturgis Offices (New York, N.Y.), 1900
  - PR21.343: Suffolk Savings Bank (Boston, Mass.), 1904
    - Interior of banking room looking toward Tremont Street. graphite and colored pencil on board., 1904 April 29 (Object PR21.343.O1)
    - Tremont Street facade. graphite and ink on trace and board., 1904 November 29 (Object PR21.343.O2)
    - Study for lettering and ornamentation. watercolor and graphite on paper and board. (Object PR21.343.O3)
    - Perspective study. charcoal on trace and board. (Object PR21.343.O4)
    - Tremont Street facade. graphite and ink on trace and board., 1904 November 29 (Object PR21.343.O5)
    - Tremont Street facade. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.343.O6)
    - Tremont Street facade. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.343.O7)
    - Elevation study. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.343.O8)
    - Perspective study. graphite and charcoal on trace and board. (Object PR21.343.O9)
    - Section looking toward Tremont Street. colored pencil on trace and board., 1904 April 25 (Object PR21.343.O10)
    - Two perspective studies. colored pencil on board. (Object PR21.343.O11)
    - Exterior perspective study. graphite on board. (Object PR21.343.O12)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-89)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-90)
  - PR21.344: Summit Avenue Houses (Saint Paul, Minn.)
  - PR21.345: Swedenborgian Church (Saint Paul, Minn.), c.1886
    - Preliminary study. watercolor on board. (Object PR21.345.O1)
  - PR21.346: Tarbox Cottage (White Bear Lake, Minn.)
    - Sketch of Cottage [exterior perspective]. ink on board., 1889 (Object PR21.346.O1)
  - PR21.347: Tennessee War Memorial
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board. (Object PR21.347.O1)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board. (Object PR21.347.O2)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board. (Object PR21.347.O3)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board., 1922 January 5 (Object PR21.347.O4)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board. (Object PR21.347.O5)
    - Front elevation studies. graphite and ink on board. (Object PR21.347.O6)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board. (Object PR21.347.O7)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on paper., 1922 January 4 (Object PR21.347.O8)
      Housed with PR21.229.O2 and PR21.355.O2
  - PR21.348: 5th Street Theatre (Saint Paul, Minn.)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-194)
  - PR21.349: Theological Seminary, Refectory Building (Saint Paul, Minn.)
  - PR21.350: Gen. Samuel Thomas, Tomb (Sleepy Hollow, N.Y.)
    - Overhead perspective. presentation. color. (Item PR21.350.O1)
    - Front perspective. graphite and watercolor on board. (Object PR21.350.O2)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-92)
  - PR21.351: Town and Country Club House (Saint Paul, Minn.), 1892
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-93)
  - PR21.351A: Tracy House
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-92)
  - PR21.352: Trans-Mississippi and International Exposition: Agricultural Building (Omaha, Neb.)
  - PR21.353: Trenton School of Industrial Arts (Trenton, N.J.)
    - Side elevation. graphite and ink wash on trace and board. (Object PR21.353.O1)
    - Sketch showing wainscoting in faience tiling. watercolor and graphite on board. (Object PR21.353.O2)
  - PR21.354: W. C. Tuckerman House (Oyster Bay, N.Y.) - McKim, Mead, and White
    - Exterior study. watercolor and graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.329/354.O1)
  - PR21.355: Union Central Life Building (Cincinatti, Ohio), 1915
    - Upper part of tower. graphite on paper. (Object PR21.355.O1)
    - Exterior perspective study. mixed media (color) on board., 1911 September 16 (Object PR21.355.O2)
      Housed with PR21.347.O8 and PR21.229.O2
    - Exterior study. photoreproduction of rendering on board. (Object PR21.355.O3)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-94)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-95)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-96)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-97)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-98)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-99)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-100)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-101)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-102)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-103)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-104)
  - PR21.356: Union Club (New York, N.Y.), 1900
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction of rendering on board. (Object PR21.356.O1)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-105)
    - Folded drawings: full scale detail (Offsite-box CG-106)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-107)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-108)
  - PR21.357: Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.)
  - PR21.358: United Congregational Church (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1918
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-109)
  - PR21.359: United States Army Supply Base [Brooklyn Army Terminal / U.S. Army Military Ocean Terminal] (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.), 1920
    - Study of pier end. watercolor and colored pencil on paper and board., 1918 June 20 (Object PR21.359.O1)
    - Perspective study showing tracks, cranes, and ships. mixed media on board. [neg. 71488], 1923 (Object PR21.359.O2)
    - Perspective study showing buildings. charcoal on board., 1918 April 21 (Object PR21.359.O3)
    - Exterior perspective study, pier end. graphite on board., 1918 (Object PR21.359.O4)
    - Interior view. photograph on board. (Object PR21.359.O5)
    - Exterior perspective study, pier end. charcoal on board., 1918 (Object PR21.359.O6)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-110)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-111)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-112)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-113)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-116)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-117)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-118)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-119)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-120)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-121)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-122)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-123)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-124)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-126)
  - PR21.360: United States Chamber of Commerce (Washington, D. C.), 1921
    - Sketch of reception room. graphite on board. (Object PR21.360.O1)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-127)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-128)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-129)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-130)
  - PR21.361: United States Courthouse [Federal Court of Appeals?] (New York, N.Y.)
    - Exterior perspective. crayon on board. (Object PR21.361.O1)
    - South elevation. graphite and ink wash. (Object PR21.361.O2)
    - Two elevation studies. graphite on trace and board., 1930 December 11 (Object PR21.361.O3)
    - Elevation study. graphite on trace and board., 1930 December 11 (Object PR21.361.O4)
    - Elevation study. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.361.O5)
    - Two exterior studies. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.361.O6)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and watercolor on board., 1930 December 30 (Object PR21.361.O7)
      Housed with PR21.295.O1
    - Folded drawings: interior detail (Offsite-box CG-131)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-132)
    - Folded drawings: 13.8, 13.9, metal and bronze work (Offsite-box CG-133)
    - Folded drawings: shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-134)
    - Folded drawings: electrical (Offsite-box CG-135)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-136)
    - Folded drawings: superseded (Offsite-box CG-137)
    - Folded drawings: carpentry (Offsite-box CG-138)
    - Folded drawings: heating/ventilation, mechanical equipment (Offsite-box CG-139)
    - Folded drawings: misc. shop drawings (Offsite-box 140)
    - Folded drawings: surveys (Offsite-box CG-141)
    - Folded drawings: surveys (Offsite-box CG-142)
  - PR21.362: United States Custom House (New York, N.Y.)
    - Early study. mixed media on brittle board., 1904 (Object PR21.362.O1)
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction of rendering on board. (Object PR21.362.O2)
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction of rendering on board. (Object PR21.362.O3)
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction of rendering removed from board. (Object PR21.362.O4)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-143)
  - PR21.363: United States Department of Justice Building (Washington, D. C.)
  - PR21.364: United States Legation (Ottawa, Ont.), 1928
    - Preliminary studies for perspective. watercolor and crayon on paper and board., 1928 September 27 (Object PR21.364.O1)
    - Interior perspective study. watercolor on board. (Object PR21.364.O2)
    - Interior perspective study. colored pencil on board. (Object PR21.364.O3)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-100)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-145)
  - PR21.365: United States Mint (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1900
  - PR21.366: United States Supreme Court Building (Washington, D. C.), 1926-1933
    - Preliminary study of front elevation. graphite on trace and board., 1928 September 18 (Object PR21.366.O1)
    - Interior of the conference rooms. graphite on trace and board., 1956 July 3 (Object PR21.366.O2)
    - Freestanding columns - wide spacing [exterior perspective]. graphite on paper., 1930 June 18 (Object PR21.366.O3)
    - Conference room [interior perspective]. graphite on board., 1931 (Object PR21.366.O4)
    - The private office of an Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States. watercolor on board., 1934 (Object PR21.366.O5)
    - Preliminary study [front elevation]. graphite and ink wash on board, 1926 November (Object PR21.366.O6)
    - Chief Justice's reception room, end wall. graphite and crayon on paper. (Object PR21.366.O7)
    - Sketch of large doors in conference room. graphite on trace and board., 1932 August 30 (Object PR21.366.O8)
    - Sketch of bay in reading room (perspective). graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.366.O9)
    - Detail of ceiling of space 330F, reading room third floor. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.366.O10)
    - Interior perspective, hallway. graphite on paper and board., 1930 August 12 (Object PR21.366.O11)
    - Detail of bay in special library, third floor. graphite on trace and board., 1932 October 28 (Object PR21.366.O12)
    - Preliminary study - second floor plan. ink on board., 1927 December 7 (Object PR21.366.O13)
    - Preliminary study - first floor plan. ink on board. (Object PR21.366.O14)
    - Decorative panel detail, conference room. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.366.O15)
    - Study for space 330E third floor. graphite on trace and board., 1932 December 27 (Object PR21.366.O16)
    - Detail of ceiling of space 330F, reading room, third floor. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.366.O17)
    - Main lobby (perspective study). graphite on paper, [circa 1932] (Object PR21.366.O18)
      housed with PR21.253.O2
    - Justices' retiring room. graphite on board., 1931 (Object PR21.366.O19)
    - Interior perspective. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.366.O20)
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction on board., 1928 February 12 (Object PR21.366.O21)
    - Interior perspective study of hallway. graphite on paper, hinged to mat., 1926 (Object PR21.366.O22)
    - Library reading room, perspective study. graphite on board. (Object PR21.366.O23)
    - Rolled and folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-147)
    - Folded shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-148)
    - Folded shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-149)
    - Folded drawings: studies (Offsite-box CG-150)
    - Folded drawings: blueprints (Offsite-box CG-151)
    - Folded shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-152)
    - Folded shop drawings: marble (Offsite-box CG-153)
    - Rolled and folded full scale detail shop drawings on trace paper (Offsite-box CG-154)
    - Folded shop drawings: HVAC, metalwork, schedules (Offsite-box CG-155)
    - Folded drawings: interior detail, marble (Offsite-box CG-156)
    - Folded shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-157)
    - Folded shop drawings: John Marshall statue (Offsite-box CG-158)
    - Rolled early studies and folded shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-159)
    - Folded shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-160)
  - PR21.367: United States Treasury Annex (Washington, D. C.), 1917
    - View of approach. watercolor on board. (Object PR21.367.O1)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue elevation. graphite and ink on board., 1917 August (Object PR21.367.O2)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue elevation. graphite and ink on board., 1917 July (Object PR21.367.O3)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-161)
  - PR21.368: University of Minnesota (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1908
    - Study [site plan]. graphite and ink on trace and board., 1907 October 26 (Object PR21.368.O1)
    - Study and rough sketch of general plan. ink on board, graphite on board., 1908 (Object PR21.368.O2)
    - Two studies of general plan. graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.368.O3)
    - Study [site plan]. ink wash on trace and board., 1907 October 29 (Object PR21.368.O4)
    - Study [site plan]. ink wash on trace and board. (Object PR21.368.O5)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-162)
  - PR21.369: University of Texas, Library and Education Building (Austin, Tex.), 1910-1914, 1920
    - Front elevation study. graphite and watercolor on trace and board. (Object PR21.369.O1)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and watercolor on trace and board. (Object PR21.369.O2)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on board. (Object PR21.369.O3)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and watercolor on trace and board. (Object PR21.369.O4)
    - Longitudinal and transverse section studies. graphite on board. (2 drawings) (Object PR21.369.O5)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and watercolor on board. (Object PR21.369.O6)
    - Main floor plan.ink on board. (Object PR21.369.O7)
    - Elevation sketch. graphite on board. (Object PR21.369.O8)
    - Preliminary study for Educational Building. watercolor, crayon, and graphite on board., 1916 July 12 (Object PR21.369.O9)
    - Study for second floor plan. graphite and crayon on trace and board., 1916 June 9 (Object PR21.369.O10)
    - Study for third floor plan. graphite and crayon on trace and board., 1916 June 9 (Object PR21.369.O11)
    - Exterior perspective study. reproduction on board. (Object PR21.369.O12)
    - Study for first floor plan. graphite and crayon on trace and board., 1916 June 9 (Object PR21.369.O13)
    - Preliminary study for Educational Building. graphite on trace and board., 1916 June 9 (Object PR21.369.O14)
    - Study of library (front elevation). graphite and watercolor on trace and board. (Object PR21.369.O15)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-162)
    - Folded drawings: Education Building (Offsite-box CG-163)
    - Folded drawings: Library Building (Offsite-box CG-164)
  - PR21.370: Virginia Avenue House (Saint Paul, Minn.)
  - PR21.371: Wabash Avenue and 10th Street Office Building (Saint Paul, Minn.)
  - PR21.372: Ward, Tomb (Newark, N.J.), 1906
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-193)
  - PR21.373: War Buildings (Washington, D. C.)
  - PR21.374: Milwaukee Warehouse (Milwaukee, Wis.)
  - PR21.375: Warner Tomb, Woodlawn Cemetery (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  - PR21.376: Warren National Bank (Warren, Pa.)
  - PR21.377: Washington D. C. Plan and Memorials, 1933
    - Site plan, unidentified monuments. graphite on board. (Object PR21.377.O1)
  - PR21.378: Washington State Capitol (Olympia, Wa.)
  - PR21.379: Waterbury Armory (Waterbury, Conn.)
    - Exterior study. watercolor and crayon on trace and board. (Object PR21.379.O1)
    - Exterior study. crayon on board - extremely friable., 1919 (Object PR21.379.O2)
  - PR21.379A: Waterbury Club (Waterbury, Conn.)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-165)
  - PR21.380: Waterbury Fountain (Waterbury, Conn.)
  - PR21.381: Waterbury Municipal Building [City Hall?] (Waterbury, Conn.), 1913
  - PR21.382: Waterbury National Bank Building (Waterbury, Conn.), 1919
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-166)
  - PR21.383: Waterbury Offices and Stores (Waterbury, Conn.)
  - PR21.383A: Waterbury School Building (Waterbury, Conn.)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-166)
  - PR21.384: Waterbury Shelter, Library Park (Waterbury, Conn.)
  - PR21.385: Waterbury Store and Office Building (Waterbury, Conn.)
  - PR21.386: Waterbury Theater (Waterbury, Conn.), 1919
  - PR21.387: D. H. Watson House
  - PR21.388: J. J. Watson House
  - PR21.389: Weckessen House
  - PR21.390: Dr. E. K. Wedelstaedt House (Saint Paul, Minn.), 1899
  - PR21.391: West Street Building (New York, N.Y.), 1905
    - Front elevation study. graphite and ink wash on trace and board. (Object PR21.391.O1)
    - Front elevation sketch. charcoal on board., 1905 May 7 (Object PR21.391.O2)
    - Front elevation study. graphite and watercolor on trace and board., 1905 (Object PR21.391.O3)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-76)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-167)
    - Folded drawings: ornamental details (Offsite-box CG-168)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-169)
    - Rolled drawings: structural (Offsite-box CG-170)
    - Folded drawings: full scale details (Offsite-box CG-190)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-194)
  - PR21.392: West Virginia State Capitol (Charleston, W. Va.), 1923
    - Sketch of rotunda, ground floor. Colored pencil on trace and board., 1929 June 11 (Object PR21.392.O1)
    - Governor's private office (perspective study). graphite on trace and board. (Object PR21.392.O2)
    - Senate and House retiring rooms (perspective study). graphite on trace and board., 1924 (Object PR21.392.O3)
    - Interior perspective study. crayon on trace and board., 1923 February 6 (Object PR21.392.O4)
    - Entrance to governor's office (perspective study). graphite on trace, matted., 1929 (Object PR21.392.O5)
    - Exterior perspective (untitled wing). graphite on board. (Object PR21.392.O6)
    - Interior perspective study for hall. crayon on trace and board. (Object PR21.392.O7)
    - Governor's private office (interior perspective study). graphite and charcoal on paper, matted. (Object PR21.392.O8)
    - Interior perspective study for hall. crayon on trace and board. (Object PR21.392.O9)
    - Interior perspective study for chamber. graphite on trace, hinged to mat. (Object PR21.392.O10)
    - House of Delegates (perspective study). reproduction on board., 1923 December (Object PR21.392.O11)
    - Supreme Court Chamber, perspective study. reproduction on board., 1923 March 1 (Object PR21.392.O12)
    - Supreme Court Chamber, perspective study. graphite on trace and board., 1923 March 1 (Object PR21.392.O13)
    - Governor's reception room, perspective study. graphite on trace., 1929 (Object PR21.392.O14)
    - Senate Chamber, perspective study. photoreproduction on board. (Object PR21.392.O15)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-171)
  - PR21.393: Westchester Avenue Railroad Station (Bronx, N.Y.)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-172)
  - PR21.394: Western Cities Trust Company Building (Minneapolis, Minn.)
    - Rolled drawings (Offsite-box CG-194)
  - PR21.395: Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Company (East Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - PR21.396: Wheelock Memorial (Saint Paul, Minn.), 1906
  - PR21.397: White Bear Lake Public School (White Bear Lake, Minn.)
  - PR21.398: Williams Realty Company Warehouse (New York, N.Y.), 1927
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-173)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-174)
  - PR21.399: Winfield Building
  - PR21.400: E. W. Winter, Summit Avenue House (Saint Paul, Minn.), 1892
  - PR21.401: Woolworth Building (New York, N.Y.), 1910
    - Progress plan of foundation. mixed media on linen and board., 1911 March (Object PR21.401.O1)
    - Study (exterior perspective). graphite and colored pencil on board., 1910 October (Object PR21.401.O2)
    - Preliminary study, corner of Broadway and Park Place. photoreproduction of drawing, matted., 1910 (Object PR21.401.O3)
    - Three photographs: Exterior eye-level view of entrance; two prints of exterior back view. photographs removed from board. (Object PR21.401.O4)
    - View from City Hall Park. matted photograph removed from board. (Object PR21.401.O5)
    - Study [Park Place elevation]. watercolor on photoreproduction removed from board., 1910 May 3 (Object PR21.401.O6)
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction of rendering removed from board. (Object PR21.401.O7)
    - Cutout front and side elevation studies. watercolor and graphite on board. (Object PR21.401.O8)
    - Exterior perspective study. photoreproduction of rendering removed from board., 1911 (Object PR21.401.O9)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-173)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-175)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-176)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-177)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-178)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-179)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-180)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-181)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-182)
    - Folded drawings: shop drawings (Offsite-box CG-183)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-184)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-185)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-186)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-187)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-188)
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-189)
  - PR21.402: Woolworth Memorial Church (Great Bend, N.J.), 1913
  - PR21.403: Woolworth Office (Watertown, N.Y.)
  - PR21.404: World Columbian Exposition: Minnesota Building (Chicago, Ill.), 1893
  - PR21.405: Worthington Building (Saint Paul, Minn.)
  - PR21.406: Yeaman's Hall (Charleston, S.C.), 1915
  - PR21.407: YMCA Building (New York, N.Y.)
  - PR21.408: York Safe and Lock Company (York, Pa.)
  - PR21.409: Yorktown Forum (Yorktown, Va.), 1929
  - PR21.410: George Young, Tomb (Edgartown, Mass.), 1906
    - Folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-193)
  - PR21.411: Zumbrota Hotel (Zumbrota, Minn.)
  - PR21.412: Unidentified Bridge
    - Perspective from street. watercolor on board., 1930 (Object PR21.412.O1)
  - Unidentified Church
  - PR21.413B: Unidentified House
    - Perspective study. watercolor on board. (Object PR21.413B.O1)
  - PR21.414: Unidentified Monument, 1896